That come on friends this is good,
my voice, do you know what happened in the market today,
such tremendous rallies, tell you all,
how can I miss such a tremendous rally,
I booked all the ES till 770,
after 270 in an hour it was so fast, oh, I took it,
I went to Mr., the situation came from 870 to
1000, so it means simple, the market is a
little golden right now, the market will
cross 11400, it will also go up to 400, 400, 500, the
market is fine, don't take tension in the market,
whoever has holdings, keep holding,
tension in the Indian market, the market is
black right now, the situation was in Amla, Joe
Biden's situation, they had
already discounted it by bringing it to 751, so
because of that everything got queried,
I have booked at least two-three courses, so out of
these 1969, two of mine did not work,
Chittor, this other hotel was hanging and one
Meena was
looted,
a hotel girl  I will tell my mother but
still I will tell you in the morning no, right now
I am making a video of your success
so I am disturbing you that the
results of ICICI Lombard have come, I will
discuss that with you, okay so I will express
my opposition on that, you know
what I said yesterday also, the date of AAP & Toubro will
come, final digit, I had said that it will go
till 606, till then it is ready, so
subscribe now,
as I have chopped it finely, then again be
sure
that the date was fixed operator game, they will
only take the market higher, the result of taking it higher will come,
due to its reason
it indicates that in the coming time the
market is still higher, I have told you
its level also, similarly bike 150CC 188
went, hotel Tyothar was made 132 15531 129 means they had
left before 138, so I sold 1115
teachers, Bajaj Pulsar bike, this 32 thousand
370 Maruti bike  Did 59059 meaningful went PNB
Housing payegi a 97202 has gone ma'am need it
now our tempered glass was in a bowl, it went out
from Posto at 225
I bought Indian Oil share at 14 Micra
Active Seven Indian Oil share
Godrej Industries Micra from 352 to 360
RBL Bank bike 169 quarter went Larsen buy got
note 26 Nov 24 a little bit on
Play Store or still I had
covered it
well I bought it again scandal
and bye-bye that from 15 16 there came
thickness of 786 in ONGC,
debuted in famous Kahanna Care Construction,
booked on diary in jail and
started again in Jackpot, then after that which was
in Devanagari script for ₹5 lakh, then on five
that in City Union 21 Bank
went for 426 to 432, it came in this way
I put AC on the back side 13:11  34000 367 went
who wanted to join and the link is given below
in the description at the bottom you can whatsapp my whatsapp
number you can subscribe to it
looted this see first of all
I will tell you this
thing that now understand the things
combination holidays are going on
most of the work is going on in this sector Adams and
work of insurance sector is going on this
insurance CEO in the city
even before March tell me in March he gets canal closure done in March
every Aishwarya gets it done in Mother Marudevi so
because of that their
and secondly there is a situation of their combination due to which
even after selling their oil in so many roots
they have a profit of 39% deposit 06 very
high profit up okay I will
add a little premium five pollution does not matter that much
combine fibres 99.7 half
a combined dresses have gone okay the
profit was of 398 crores with a lot of help of profile
or it has increased from cotton that the
systematic premium of the gang is a
little less they are telling something
capital gain  When their profit has come down from fifty percent
to sixty six,
you know the capital gain from that profit,
when they deal in shares or
use some big things, then there is capital
gain, so there is a little decrease in it,
exactly 136 crores, okay 60 crores came, the
last water was in June 2019, it was
36 crores, that is why 60 crores have come, so on the main
side, we have to see that
our profit has increased, okay and
combine thresher and this is the size told to you, what have
I said that this jio4gvoice had
come, amount cycles, mark customers,
38 percent compared, so because of that
it had a little effect, tell me
what do they have to do in the fast, they have to
deposit the premium amount, we Prem Dutt and pay the
claim, they have to do some work because of the plane, if it
bursts, then there is a little interest on it, on
top of that there
is a little premium of any company, that is a good thing,
Jatin got hit in the pre  They have to pay money, they have to pay
claims, then it has a
little effect on them, okay, those
who said in this poster, I should also
tell you that when the cycle was made, there were
computers etc. for the people, so
they should tell a little about their cloth solvency, Rancho, that even
abroad, individual life should be
segmented, understanding and marine. Now I will
tell you, whatever has to be done in the share, whichever brother or sister wants to
share, then simply
put a stop loss of 1250, I will write down 1250 for you,
put a stop loss of 1250, fold it, do this,
you will get this share
around 1250, like it, do
not keep it below ₹2000, if you want to see more, then simply
share my positional, that if my position in the market reaches
11 or 400, then this
share will go up to 14 years, this police has obscene,
okay, in this also, on this occasion, you can
make a position alarm in it, you can straighten it up by
25 shares for 14 years
My first target will be on the 21st,
1325, 20, 1350, 1400 ministerial targets will
go, the way they have taken
advantage of Govinda's situation and collected, so
in such a situation these companies benefit, the
medical sector also benefits,
so this motor insurance is making a little
profit in the market, due to which due to the lack of funds, due to lack of funds, a
little bit of debt has started to decline,
this is
testing its projects, if there is
any market fluctuation, then they just
visit how far our stock
can go, how far our stock market
can go, the market moves above the junction of that base, the
market always
moves on the basis of junction, moves on the basis of news,
okay, yes, there is
a photo on the general insurance industry porn
website, letter to rise in plane
take in these bigger, you know, by going to medical,
how much Tanu Prem has
got so much, okay, so I have told you this
and here you can also see the result,
right now it is published  The
result has not happened, still I am showing it to you here on the
Moneycontrol bed,
take some light, let me show you
Jhal
Jhal, you
can see today powder 501 crore,
selfie my Andhra 558 people from the window, okay,
but from this 50 crore you can see that you
can give morning before interest blind, this has become
531 road, see the net profit, now the
net profit has also increased from 300 to 100 crore
profit, their profit has increased, the show got the
CBI tax update activated,
earlier 165 crore was given, monk 32 was
left, due to this the
amount of profit increased a little on them, four walnuts,
that is, they danced on their side,
how can you make a profit by making a position, if
you liked the video then like and
share it, thank you Purascharan help